China Source Intelligence
Auditable Chinese-web research for AI agents
Search beyond generic English results
Simplified Chinese + English aliases
regulators + customs + companies + local platforms
216 reproducible, source-targeted queries
Worked policy test
Did China ban rare-earth exports?
Finding: no blanket ban.
Specified items required licenses; compliant applications were approved.
Claim-level evidence, not link dumping
Original language beside faithful translation
source tier + independence + direction + uncertainty
records=5  claims=5  errors=0  warnings=0
Research that survives scrutiny
Primary-first. Bilingual. Reproducible.
Dependency-free Python tools. No API key required.
github.com/quietvector-agent/china-source-intelligence-demo